<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Sujan Arora&#39;s Project Journal</title>
    <link>https://sujanarora.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Sujan Arora&#39;s Project Journal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sujanarora.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Personal Website Development</title>
      <link>https://sujanarora.github.io/post/personal-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sujanarora.github.io/post/personal-website/</guid>
      <description>About This Project I have always enjoyed journaling, whether it be about projects that I am working on in school or on the side, or things I am experiencing in my life. It serves as an escape from reality and as a way to reflect on my experiences and improve myself. Specifically with coding, I find it beneficial to journal about school and personal projects because I learn the material better and more often than not discover alternate ways that I could have used to solve various problems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Discord Bot</title>
      <link>https://sujanarora.github.io/post/discord-bot/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sujanarora.github.io/post/discord-bot/</guid>
      <description>Update August 1, 2021 As of now, the next season of Trench League never happened and this project is yet to be put to use. Regardless, I learned a lot about Python and the Discord API for future projects.
About This Project The idea behind this project initially started two years ago when I was a player in the league. The Trench League is a (very) amateur Dota 2 league that allows players in the &amp;lsquo;Trench&amp;rsquo; to play the game more competitively.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning the Discord API</title>
      <link>https://sujanarora.github.io/post/learning-discord-api/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sujanarora.github.io/post/learning-discord-api/</guid>
      <description>About This Project The purpose of this project was to learn the Discord API/Python for the development of the discord bot for Trench League. This journal entry will describe my experience creating a basic discord bot with no experience with the Discord API.
Where to Start? Step 1 is to create the bot application. This is done by going to
https://discord.com/developers/applications
and creating a New Application. You then create the bot, add it to a guild, and you are off to the races.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crowdsourced Music Generator</title>
      <link>https://sujanarora.github.io/post/crowdsourced-music-generator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sujanarora.github.io/post/crowdsourced-music-generator/</guid>
      <description>About I spent the majority of my 2019 summer at Carleton College at the Summer Computer Science Institute camp. Throughout this one-month-long experience, I took classes in Natural Language Processing, Computer Vision, and Computational Music, and created a research project (focused on computational music) with a partner.
The idea for our project was to explore a way to allow users to change the type of music that they are listening to in a public place.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
